YULIIA DOBROVA

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

yuliia.dobrova@gmail.com

Vancouver, BC, Canada

+1(778)-325-3487

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuliia-dobrova/

https://github.com/YuliaDobrova

SUMMARY

Experienced Full-Stack Software Developer with a history of more than 5 years in creating of applications and websites. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, RestAPI, Github, Node.js. Created solo projects and participated in collaborative Git usage with team. Technical background in Civil Design-Engineering, offering over 10 years of both executive and management positions.

Currently I am looking for a full-time position as a Full-Stack Software Developer, willing to strengthen the team with my skills and desire to create, fix, innovate.

HARD SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

· Team leadership · Public Speaking

- HTML5
- React
- Rest API
- Bootstrap
- Responsibility
- Problem Solving

- CSS3 JavaScript
- Github
- Redux Toolkit MongoDB Node.js
- jQuery Material-Ul
- Curiosity
- Collaborative Development

- TypeScript
- Deployment
 Express.js
 JSON
- Flexibility
- Agile Methodologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research and production enterprise "Ukrradioprom" LLC · Freelance Full-Stack Software Developer

April 2023 - January 2024

 Developed a user-friendly web application to efficiently handle clients product database. That resulted in a significant 20% increase in online sales within a period of 6 months.

"Web Tech Company "TensionX" ("SaaS Insiders") · Full-time Front-end Developer

February 2022 - March 2023

- Contributed to collaborative Git practices while working with a team of up to 7 developers, successfully delivering to the customer a social media platform meeting deadline in 3 months.
- · Created markup and styles according to the design for Mobile & Web Application, developed authorization forms with validation, processed data exchange with the backend, established block for the comments and their display in real time (WebSocket), implemented text translation for the entire application, improved user functionality.
- Developed and improved user functionality in an existing School Management System application.

Dental Center of Dr. Krolyk · Freelance Front-end Software Developer

November 2021 - January 2022

· Created a website design from scratch and developed it for my client in 2 months (implemented interactivity, real reviews, geolocation, multilingualism, adapted to different devices, deployed to hosting).

Engineering Company "Avtomagistral" LCC · Full-time

September 2018 - February 2021

- Civil Design Engineer / Head of the Project Department / Front-end Developer
- Holding the title of Civil Design Engineer with the certificate (license), created drawings in AutoCAD, was engaged in project approvals, supervised the author's projects during construction.
- Managed a team of 30 diverse engineers: geodetic engineers, design engineers, accountant engineers.
- · Completed of 50 infrastructure building projects for new design or reconstruction (roads, bridges, park areas, networks) within a 6 month period meeting deadline.
- Created a multi-page business card website for our company from scratch.

EDUCATION

Backend Basics Bootcamp

March 2024

OneCodeCamp Academy

Full-stack Developer Course

September 2020 - October 2021

GoIT Global - International ed-tech company

Master's Degree in Water Resources Engineering

September 2005 - June 2011

The Faculty of Geography of National University of Kyiv

LANGUAGES

• English (Fluent) Français (Intermediate)

Ukrainian (Fluent)

Russian (Fluent)